Internal network abuse matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Cloud metadata exploitation matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Trust boundary violations matters because applications often enforce access,
process sensitive information, connect to business systems,
and create operational evidence.
Teams should evaluate this issue across user-facing features, APIs, administrative tools,
cloud services, and delivery pipelines.
Network segmentation URL validation Egress filtering Selected ISO mappings for this topic
include 8.
20 - Network security; 8.
22 - Segregation of networks; 8.
23 - Web filtering.